<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>http://tiffanylo.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:17:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tiffanylo.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meringue</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</guid>
      <description>Meringue captures all the delight and swoopiness of cake lettering, packaged into a neat display typeface. It has generous curves and spacing, with minimal overlaps, as a nod to the constraints posed by frosting as a substrate and a piping bag as a writing tool. Think wide letters for easier handling, minimal stroke overlaps to decrease areas with too much frosting, broad curves made by physically moving the arm/body, and a tail formed by a baker pulling the piping bag up and away upon finishing a letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Um, Berella</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</guid>
      <description>Um, Berella is a flared serif typeface family inspired by the style, attitude, and vision of Rihanna — global pop sensation, style and cultural icon, entrepreneur, and designer. Its snatched waists, accentuated curves, assertive joins, and tension between its outer curvature and inner obtuse angles borrow the common tropes exhibited by Rihanna&amp;rsquo;s design preferences. The geometry involves pointed shapes, but rarely uses boring right angles and triangles. The features are drawn decisively and full of attention to construction, with no frilliness or extraneousness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life!&amp;rdquo; is a personal mantra that I keep to remain thankful and optimistic despite the demands of everyday life. This poster is a party with vibrant colors, bold typography, and enough confetti to last all night long. Everything was hand-cut and drawn with love and care. It was an extremely time-consuming process. However, it was great fun to return to my papercraft roots and experiment organically throughout the design iterations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begin Anywhere</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>Begin Anywhere. A simple mantra that’s much harder to put into practice.
Rather than approaching the poster design on Illustrator or with ink + paper, I decided to open myself up to a new medium/approach — A ball of coral yarn and a large blank poster board to design on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archer</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/archer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 02:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/archer/</guid>
      <description>A type specimen to feature Archer&amp;rsquo;s versatility as a modern, savvy, and approachable typeface.
Slab serif fonts aren&amp;rsquo;t typically go-to options for designers, but this exploration of Archer as body text, title text, and decorative elements demonstrates all of its potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Year in Books</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/thoughts/2021_year_in_books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/thoughts/2021_year_in_books/</guid>
      <description>Top 10
The Secret Life of Groceries The Office of Historical Corrections Convenience Store Woman Lurking Goodbye, again Detransition, Baby The Anthropocene Reviewed The Joy of Being Selfish Steal like an Artist Cook Real Hawaii The Ocean at the End of the Lane The Secret Life of Groceries I took months to finish this book — Not because it was a slog, but because I enjoyed it too much and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to binge it all in one go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Hiya! I’m Tif. Currently, I&#39;m seeking full-time or freelance opportunities in brand/editorial design, remote or based in Boston, MA. Graphic design, photography, pop culture, and food occupy the majority of my brain cells/hours. I&#39;ve recently received my certificate in Typeface Design from TypeParis and completed Type Electives&#39; Foundations in Display Type Design course. Previously, I worked as a fullstack Lead Software Developer at athenaHealth, helping healthcare professionals do their jobs with greater ease.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
