<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>https://tiffanylo.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tiffanylo.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gen Bakes</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</guid>
      <description>Background Gen Bakes is a popular microbakery and popup run by brilliant baker, running community fixture, and energetic dynamo Genevieve Huang. She bakes cakes, cookies, tarts, and all sorts of other delicious treats for clients throughout the month and hosts monthly popup events in the Boston area to sell her treats.&#xA;Brand Strategy A quick look through Gen&amp;rsquo;s Instagram feed where she documents her many baking projects will have you craving for a delicious and beautiful treat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks like Art, Tastes like Feet</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/looks-like-art-tastes-like-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/looks-like-art-tastes-like-feet/</guid>
      <description>Background The world of craft beer today is colorful, fun, and incredibly expressive. It&amp;rsquo;s also flavorful, but as someone who does not enjoy beer, the cans always appealed to me visually above anything else.&#xA;Looks like Art, Tastes like Feet is a study on craft beer can artwork, memorializing the beer can collection of the unofficial Grand Somerville Beer Can Art Gallery.&#xA;Layout Everything works together, thanks to a consistent color scheme, shared condensed proportions to the typefaces, a strict grid system, and standardized photography setup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilachand Honors College Symposium</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/khc-symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/khc-symposium/</guid>
      <description>Background Every year, the Boston Univeristy Kilachand Honors College hosts a symposium where graduating seniors present their keystone projects across academic disciplines to the greater BU community. At the heart of the Kilachand Honors College program is the mission of fostering interdisciplinary thinking led by the heart and mind, to embody the idea of &amp;ldquo;Only connect&amp;rdquo; as described in E.M. Forster&amp;rsquo;s Howard&amp;rsquo;s End. Keystone projects ranged from analyses of operating room efficiencies to the history and influence of loanwords on the Japanese language to the impact of hegemonic masculinity on male fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston University Women in Computer Science (WiCS) Branding</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</guid>
      <description>Background BU WiCS is an organization focused on fostering a sense of community and empowering students in the BU Computer Science department, with a focus on female students who have historically been significantly out-numbered in the department.&#xA;The board members wanted new branding that felt more inviting, more engaging, and more memorable.&#xA;Logo The use of a monoline script BU WiCS wordmark conveys the friendliness and personal nature of the group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meringue</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</guid>
      <description>Background Meringue captures all the delight and swoopiness of cake lettering, packaged into a neat display typeface. It has generous curves and spacing, with minimal overlaps, as a nod to the constraints posed by frosting as a substrate and a piping bag as a writing tool.&#xA;Structure &amp;#43; Form Think wide letters for easier handling, minimal stroke overlaps to decrease areas with too much frosting, broad curves made by physically moving the arm/body, and a tail formed by a baker pulling the piping bag up and away upon finishing a letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Um, Berella</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</guid>
      <description>Background Um, Berella is a flared serif typeface family inspired by the style, attitude, and vision of Rihanna — global pop sensation, style and cultural icon, entrepreneur, and designer. Its snatched waists, accentuated curves, assertive joins, and tension between its outer curvature and inner obtuse angles borrow the common tropes exhibited by Rihanna&amp;rsquo;s design preferences.&#xA;Geometry The geometry involves pointed shapes, but rarely uses boring right angles and triangles. The features are drawn decisively and full of attention to construction, with no frilliness or extraneousness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Process &amp;ldquo;Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life!&amp;rdquo; is a personal mantra that I keep to remain thankful and optimistic despite the demands of everyday life. This poster is a party with vibrant colors, bold typography, and enough confetti to last all night long. Everything was hand-cut and drawn with love and care. It was an extremely time-consuming process. However, it was great fun to return to my papercraft roots and experiment organically throughout the design iterations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music &#43; Us</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/music-&#43;-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/music-&#43;-us/</guid>
      <description>Background Music + Us explores how we can use the lens of music and self-quantification to make data feel human in a world where big data continues to grow and data feels increasingly abstract, impersonal, and even daunting to the average individual.&#xA;The project aimed to inform audiences about data visualization history and literacy, followed by applying that understanding to music listening data collected through a survey, Billboard Hot 100 music data, and available music metadata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 Days of Type</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/26-days-of-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/26-days-of-type/</guid>
      <description>Background Every year, folks around the world participate in the 36 Days of Type project in the Spring and share in the love of letterforms.&#xA;Each letter is inspired by the work of an artist whose name started with the letter — It was a playground for testing out letterforms and adapting different visual styles to my own sensibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Begin Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>Process Begin Anywhere. A simple mantra that’s much harder to put into practice.&#xA;Rather than approaching the poster design on Illustrator or with ink + paper, I decided to open myself up to a new medium/approach — A ball of yarn and a large blank poster board to design on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Wiz</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</guid>
      <description>Process Home Wiz is a local handyman business that wanted to present their company as approachable, reliable, and trustworthy.&#xA;Raf loved the idea of incorporating the shape of a house roof in the crossbar of the H, but as I explored this idea with existing typefaces, it was clear why this is not a common form in other typefaces. The ends of the roof made it difficult to space the H and o evenly and the triangular form of the roof differed so drastically in form from the remaining round shapes in the word &amp;ldquo;Home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2021 Year in Books</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/thoughts/2021_year_in_books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/thoughts/2021_year_in_books/</guid>
      <description>Top 10&#xA;The Secret Life of Groceries The Office of Historical Corrections Convenience Store Woman Lurking Goodbye, again Detransition, Baby The Anthropocene Reviewed The Joy of Being Selfish Steal like an Artist Cook Real Hawaii The Ocean at the End of the Lane The Secret Life of Groceries I took months to finish this book — Not because it was a slog, but because I enjoyed it too much and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to binge it all in one go!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/about/</guid>
      <description>Hiya! I’m Tif. Graphic design, photography, pop culture, and food occupy the majority of my brain cells + days. I’m a freelance graphic designer with a focus on branding, lettering, and typeface design.&#xA;My practice has always been rooted in typography, joy, and collaboration.&#xA;It all began when I studied the my 2nd grade classmates’ handwriting and stole the coolest bits into my own, then designed PowerPoints and Neopets user layouts for fun.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
