<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Branding on Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>https://tiffanylo.info/tags/branding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Branding on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tiffanylo.info/tags/branding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gen Bakes</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</guid>
      <description>Background Gen Bakes is a popular microbakery and popup run by brilliant baker, running community fixture, and energetic dynamo Genevieve Huang. She bakes cakes, cookies, tarts, and all sorts of other delicious treats for clients throughout the month and hosts monthly popup events in the Boston area to sell her treats. Brand Strategy A quick look through Gen&#39;s Instagram feed where she documents her many baking projects will have you craving for a delicious and beautiful treat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston University Women in Computer Science (WiCS) Branding</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</guid>
      <description>Background BU WiCS is an organization focused on fostering a sense of community and empowering students in the BU Computer Science department, with a focus on female students who have historically been significantly out-numbered in the department. The board members wanted new branding that felt more inviting, more engaging, and more memorable. Logo The use of a monoline script BU WiCS wordmark conveys the friendliness and personal nature of the group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Wiz</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</guid>
      <description>Process Home Wiz is a local handyman business that wanted to present their company as approachable, reliable, and trustworthy. Raf loved the idea of incorporating the shape of a house roof in the crossbar of the H, but as I explored this idea with existing typefaces, it was clear why this is not a common form in other typefaces. The ends of the roof made it difficult to space the H and o evenly and the triangular form of the roof differed so drastically in form from the remaining round shapes in the word &#34;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
