<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analog on Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>http://tiffanylo.info/tags/analog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analog on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tiffanylo.info/tags/analog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weather in Boston 09.2015</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/weather-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/weather-book/</guid>
      <description>Frustrated with the inconsistency of Boston&amp;rsquo;s weather as we transitioned from Summer to Fall, I visualized the entirety of September 2015&amp;rsquo;s highs and lows every day into a compact accordion book. The comparative timeline nature of the format allows for a better overview understanding of the phenomenon experienced day in and day out in Boston.
The scale shifts from red to purple, beginning at 90+ degrees and moving down in 10-degree increments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/celebrate/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Celebrate the Mini Wins in Life!&amp;rdquo; is a personal mantra that I keep to remain thankful and optimistic despite the demands of everyday life. This poster is a party with vibrant colors, bold typography, and enough confetti to last all night long. Everything was hand-cut and drawn with love and care. It was an extremely time-consuming process. However, it was great fun to return to my papercraft roots and experiment organically throughout the design iterations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begin Anywhere</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>Begin Anywhere. A simple mantra that’s much harder to put into practice.
I decided to open myself up to a new medium/approach — A ball of coral yarn and a large blank poster board to design on. The entire piece is interconnected, with no clear indication of where the thread begins.
Another form of tactile lettering I attempted was popup lettering. I tried to play with perspective and lines with arrangement of the words to interpret the looseness that the mantra &amp;ldquo;begin anywhere&amp;rdquo; encourages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
