<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lettering on Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>http://tiffanylo.info/tags/lettering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lettering on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:05:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tiffanylo.info/tags/lettering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music &#43; Us</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/music-&#43;-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/music-&#43;-us/</guid>
      <description>Music + Us explores how we can use the lens of music and self-quantification to make data feel human in a world where big data continues to grow and data feels increasingly abstract, impersonal, and even daunting to the average individual.
The project aimed to inform audiences about data visualization history and literacy, followed by applying that understanding to music listening data collected through a survey, Billboard Hot 100 music data, and available music metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston University Women in Computer Science (WiCS) Branding</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/wics/</guid>
      <description>BU WiCS is an organization focused on fostering a sense of community and empowering students in the BU Computer Science department, with a focus on female students who have historically been significantly out-numbered in the department.
Prior logos for the organization emphasized the technical nature of the organization, but the board members wanted new branding that felt more inviting, more engaging, and more eye-catching.
The use of a monoline script BU WiCS wordmark to convey the friendliness and personal nature of the group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Wiz</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/home-wiz/</guid>
      <description>Home Wiz is a local handyman business that wanted to present their company as approachable, reliable, and trustworthy. Their previous logo missed the mark with its sleepy wizard in pajamas and skinny typeface selection.
Raf loved the idea of incorporating the shape of a house roof in the crossbar of the H, but as I explored this idea with existing typefaces, it was clear why this is not a common form in other typefaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begin Anywhere</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</guid>
      <description>Begin Anywhere. A simple mantra that’s much harder to put into practice.
Rather than approaching the poster design on Illustrator or with ink + paper, I decided to open myself up to a new medium/approach — A ball of yarn and a large blank poster board to design on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26 Days of Type</title>
      <link>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/26-days-of-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tiffanylo.info/projects/26-days-of-type/</guid>
      <description>Every year, folks around the world participate in the 36 Days of Type project in the Spring and share in the love of letterforms.
Each letter is inspired by the work of an artist whose name started with the letter — It was a playground for testing out letterforms and adapting different visual styles to my own sensibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
