<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Type Design on Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>https://tiffanylo.info/tags/type-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Type Design on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:35:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tiffanylo.info/tags/type-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meringue</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 22:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/meringue/</guid>
      <description>Background Meringue captures all the delight and swoopiness of cake lettering, packaged into a neat display typeface. It has generous curves and spacing, with minimal overlaps, as a nod to the constraints posed by frosting as a substrate and a piping bag as a writing tool. Structure &amp;#43; Form Think wide letters for easier handling, minimal stroke overlaps to decrease areas with too much frosting, broad curves made by physically moving the arm/body, and a tail formed by a baker pulling the piping bag up and away upon finishing a letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Um, Berella</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 16:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/umberella/</guid>
      <description>Background Um, Berella is a flared serif typeface family inspired by the style, attitude, and vision of Rihanna — global pop sensation, style and cultural icon, entrepreneur, and designer. Its snatched waists, accentuated curves, assertive joins, and tension between its outer curvature and inner obtuse angles borrow the common tropes exhibited by Rihanna&#39;s design preferences. Geometry The geometry involves pointed shapes, but rarely uses boring right angles and triangles. The features are drawn decisively and full of attention to construction, with no frilliness or extraneousness.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
