<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on Tiffany Lo</title>
    <link>https://tiffanylo.info/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on Tiffany Lo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tiffanylo.info/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gen Bakes</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/gen-bakes/</guid>
      <description>Background Gen Bakes is a popular microbakery and popup run by brilliant baker, running community fixture, and energetic dynamo Genevieve Huang. She bakes cakes, cookies, tarts, and all sorts of other delicious treats for clients throughout the month and hosts monthly popup events in the Boston area to sell her treats. Brand Strategy A quick look through Gen&#39;s Instagram feed where she documents her many baking projects will have you craving for a delicious and beautiful treat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looks like Art, Tastes like Feet</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/looks-like-art-tastes-like-feet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/looks-like-art-tastes-like-feet/</guid>
      <description>Background The world of craft beer today is colorful, fun, and incredibly expressive. It&#39;s also flavorful, but as someone who does not enjoy beer, the cans always appealed to me visually above anything else. Looks like Art, Tastes like Feet is a study on craft beer can artwork, memorializing the beer can collection of the unofficial Grand Somerville Beer Can Art Gallery. Layout Everything works together, thanks to a consistent color scheme, shared condensed proportions to the typefaces, a strict grid system, and standardized photography setup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Begin Anywhere</title>
      <link>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tiffanylo.info/projects/begin-anywhere/</guid>
      <description> Process Begin Anywhere. A simple mantra that’s much harder to put into practice. Rather than approaching the poster design on Illustrator or with ink + paper, I decided to open myself up to a new medium/approach — A ball of yarn and a large blank poster board to design on. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
